== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
(Penny:)So, you really
gonna break up with her?
(Raj:)Yeah, I think so.
Do you have any advice?
(Penny:)Well, I have broken up
with my fair share of guys.
(Penny:)I mean, how many times
did I break up with Leonard?
(Leonard:)I stopped
counting at four.
(Penny:)All right, my advice to you
is do it at her place
(Penny:)so you can leave
when you need to,
(Penny:)uh, tell the truth,
make it quick
(Penny:)and be prepared for tears.
(Raj:)Oh, I'm gonna do a pre-cry
before I go in there.
(Raj:)Really dry myself out.
(Leonard:)She meant Emily.
No, I-I really didn't.
(Emily:)You're seriously
breaking up with me?
(Leonard:)Yeah.
(Emily:)And you thought
right before Valentine's Day
(Emily:)was a good time to do it?
(Raj:)You're right...
let's talk again in a few days.
(Raj(on phone):)Hey, Claire.
Hi. It's-it's Rajesh.
I was-I was wondering if you're
free for Valentine's Day?
(Claire:)Sorry, I just got back
with my boyfriend.
(Raj:)But I just broke up
with my girlfriend.
(Claire:)Right before Valentine's Day?